Now, let me start by asking you, Sebas,
do I need to explain to you
what I am doing here?
No, there is no need.
Is something the matter, Sebas?
You're sweating something awful.
I'll lend you my handkerchief.
I have brought her.
Come on in, Tuare,
the human pet that Sebas took in.
You have courage to not run away.
--On your knees--
--No. Control spells are unnecessary.
To extol her courage,
I will permit her indecorum before me.
First, why don't I tell you my name?
I am Ains Ooal Gown.
I am the master of Sebas over there.
R-Right.
Now then, Sebas, I thought
I instructed you to act in a way
that would not draw attention.
Yes, my lord.
Nonetheless, you have courted trouble
for the sake of this no-account woman.
Am I wrong?
I am deeply sorry that my indiscretion
has earned your displeasure, Lord Ains,
and I will be more than mindful that
something like this never happens again.
Enough. Everyone makes mistakes.
Sebas, I will forgive your trivial blunder.
Lord Ains, I am most grateful.
However! You must
make amends for your mistake.
Kill her.
What... did you say?
Sebas, are you a dog that obeys
the Supreme One-- that obeys the 41?
Or are you someone
who believes his own will is correct?
--Well, I--
--You need not answer!
Demonstrate it to me through results.
What are you...?!
Sebas, back away!
Yes, my lord.
Cocytus, was that attack undeniably
and deliberately intended to kill her?
Without a doubt.
In that case, I take it as proof
that Sebas's loyalty is unfeigned.
Good work, Sebas.
Yes, my lord.
Now, let's move on to the next topic.
Sebas, I have evaluated that your work here
has gathered enough information.
I have decided that we will vacate the mansion,
and withdraw to Nazarick.
As for the fate of the woman,
give me some time.
I do not think it will be death, but know
that this determination is not absolute.
Demiurge, I will be taking Victim back with me.
Right.
Greater Teleportation!
She appears to be fatigued.
I will let her get some rest in her room.
I will take her there. This is no longer
a matter. Am I right, Lord Demiurge?
I suppose. You are correct, Sebas.
I have no intention of apologizing.
However, if I had
gone about this some other way,
things would not have ended up this way.
Lord Sebas...
You go and live happily in the world of humans.
Lord Ains should be able
to perform memory manipulation.
Erase all of your bad memories, and live.
What about you, Lord Sebas?
Let's have him erase
your memories of me, as well.
There is nothing good
to remember about me, after all.
What do you mean, nothing good?
My happiness comes from
being with you, Lord Sebas!
I do not think of this place as hell.
You gave me meals to fill my belly,
and a decent job to do.
I was born and raised in a small village.
My life there was a difficult one, as well.
Even after plowing the fields
while our tummies were grumbling,
the feudal lord took away
most of the crops that grew,
leaving next to nothing
to go into our own mouths.
Not to mention that in our lord's view,
we were simply playthings.
Even when I screamed,
he would keep laughing as he violated me...
I...!
All right.
It may mean your death.
If I am to be killed by you, Lord Sebas...
...by you, the gentleman
who offered me his warmth
when I was destined to die back there...
Tuare, I will ask Lord Ains to let me
take you back with me to Nazarick.
Thank you very much.
Let me verify one thing first.
Do you have any attachments
to the world of humans?
I would... kind of like to see
my younger sister again.
But my desire not to remember
any of the past is stronger still.
Very well. You go to your room.
I will go and see Lord Ains again.
Okay.
That was prickly.
I've never shared a happy kiss before.
I have returned.
Is something the matter? Your face is flushed.
It is nothing, Lord Demiurge.
You need not use that title with me.
I don't need it, either.
All right.
Thank you for greeting me. Rise.
Now then, Demiurge, I trust your
anxious mind has now been satisfied?
I never once thought
that Sebas would betray me.
I am terribly sorry for that.
Further, I thank you so much
for acknowledging my viewpoint
when I voiced my objection
to your decision, Lord Ains.
It is no matter. I have oversights, as well.
Now, you wished to discuss how to
deal with that human woman, Sebas?
Yes, my lord.
You worry that after the woman is released,
she could leak information
about Nazarick, is that it?
Then after her memories are manipulated,
you can give her some money
and leave her in a suitable place.
Lord Ains, I believe that killing her
would be a more certain way.
Stop. I do not much like homicidal acts
when they gain me nothing.
Understood. Well, shall I put her to work
at the stockyard that I oversee?
Ah, the one where you keep the chimeras?
Lord Ains...
Hmm? What is it, Sebas?
If you are willing, I was thinking that
I would like to put Tuare to work
in the Great Tomb of Nazarick.
I once asked the same thing of Cocytus,
but Sebas, how would that benefit me?
My lord, Tuare can prepare meals.
There are only a few people
in Nazarick that can cook.
I think it would be better
to have a few others who can cook.
Indeed, I, too, found that
a point bearing consideration.
But can she prepare food
that is worthy of Nazarick?
What Tuare can cook
appears to be household fare.
If you ask whether that is worthy of Nazarick...
I do not think that
dishes such as steamed potatoes
should be served at Nazarick.
I cannot help but wonder if your thinking
is too hasty, Lord Demiurge.
If she can do home cooking,
she can also master other kinds of cooking.
We should look to the future.
In that case, I should like her to help out
with the cooking at my stockyard.
Making mincemeat for
Abelion Sheep is no easy chore.
I would be against that...
Ulbert-san, don't you remember
us talking about going to get
the rare drop from Surt, the Fire Giant Boss?
You're the one who
doesn't remember, Touch-san.
There are those here who have to
go do the Ice Dragon hunt
before they can fulfill the requirements
to change their class.
Surt's normal drop rate is lower than dragons,
so don't you think we should
take care of that first?
Touch-san, I don't think
you should act so spoiled.
No, you're the one who's
acting spoiled, Ulbert-san.
We shouldn't just be
focusing on drop rates to...
--...I am not trying to assign blame for--
--Shut up already!
We are in the presence of Lord Ains!
Ah! Lord Ains, pardon us
for carrying on in front of you!
I am sorry you had to
see us behave so foolishly.
I do not mind! I forgive you. I forgive you!
That's it! We could use
a little bickering like this!
Tch, inhibited, huh?
I'd like to see this woman Tuare. Bring her here.
Huh? Ah... Yes, as you wish!
You resemble her.
Thanks for coming, Tuare.
I have questions for you.
If you speak untruthfully, we are done talking,
and if I don't get the answer I want,
we are done as well.
Now, tell me your full name.
Tuare-- Tuareninya Veyron.
You don't say. Okay, tell me, Tuareninya,
is your desire to go to the Great Tomb
of Nazarick, and live there?
You also have the choice of
me giving you a great deal of wealth,
and taking it to live in a land
far away from here.
I-I would stay with Lord Sebas.
Very well.
Listen up, my servants...
Yes, my lord!
In the name of Ains Ooal Gown,
Tuareninya will henceforth
be under my protection!
You may be welcomed in as my guest,
but what are your wishes?
Th-Thank you very much,
but please, allow me
to work alongside Lord Sebas.
If that is your desire.
Very well, Tuareninya shall work
directly under Sebas as a provisional maid.
At the same time, the Pleiades
will have Sebas removed as team leader,
and with the addition of
youngest sister Aureole Omega,
transition to become the Pléiades.
Yuri Alpha will serve as deputy leader.
Also, inform all those
in the Great Tomb of Nazarick
that Tuareninya is under the protection
of the name of Ains Ooal Gown,
and concurrently,
will be working alongside them.
Demiurge, do you have
any objections to my decision?
None in the least.
Then to confirm, all of the sentries
posted in this mansion
will return to Nazarick at once.
Sebas and Solution, prepare to withdraw.
--Yes, my lord.
--Lord Ains...
--What is it, Demiurge?
The Abelion Sheep are omnivores,
so I would like to take this opportunity
to procure a small amount of grain.
I see.
Sebas, before you withdraw,
purchase a large amount of grain,
and deliver it to Demiurge for me.
As you wish.
Lord Ains, did you know that girl?
I believe it is right, you see,
to return kindness for kindness,
and evil for evil.
That one should make sure
to pay back one's debts.
This is the diary of...
...a young girl whose older sister
was kidnapped by aristocrats,
and who burned with fury inside.
This diary provided me with a general
knowledge of this world to some degree.
Which makes me indebted to her.
I will take the debt I incurred from you,
and pay it back to your sister.
Lord Ains, there is one request
I would like to make of you.
After reading the material that Sebas provided,
there is one place that I would like to go see.
Could I impose on you for some time?
I don't mind. You are acting for
the benefit of Nazarick, aren't you?
Go on ahead, Demiurge.
Thank you very much.
Solution and I are now
going to acquire some grain
and to pay our respects to some acquaintances.
All right...
In the meantime,
keep an eye on things here, Tuare.
Very... well... Lord Sebas...
Last night, Climb captured the head
of Eight Fingers' slave trade division.
Not too shabby of him.
As such, I think we should alter our plans,
by launching simultaneous raids today,
and taking down all of
their strongholds at once.
If too much time passes,
it will put us at a greater disadvantage.
Y-Yes, but Princess,
I thought we were short-handed.
Which is why I am thinking of enlisting
the help of a nobleman I can trust.
I have brought them.
I am here in response to
your summons, Princess Renner.
Yo, half-sister.
This sounded like it would be interesting,
so I decided to attend.
Brother?
Thank you for coming, Marquis Raeven.
I would like to ask your advice.
My advice, you say?
I believe no one in all the court
is better versed in these matters
than you are, Marquis Raeven.
This is bitter.
Shall I have some
fruit-infused water brought here?
Doesn't matter.
The maids who serve in the palace
are surprisingly fast when it comes
to informing their own houses, after all.
So, what is it that you
would like to speak about?
Don't ask for too much. Even Marquis Raeven,
one of the Six Great Nobles,
and member of the Noble Faction,
has his position to consider.
I would like to ask you, as one who is
secretly coordinating the Royal Faction,
if you would be able to mobilize the soldiers?
Ordinarily, it might have been best
to first speak to the three Great Nobles
who are connected with the Royal Faction.
However, one of them, Marquis Blumrush,
is feeding information to the Empire, isn't he?
I would ask you to wait just a moment!
You knew, right? You, who are
secretly known as the opportunist bat,
all the while guiding both
the Royal Faction and the Noble Faction,
acting to make sure that
the kingdom does not collapse?
That is why you restrict things
such that little important information
makes it to Marquis Blumrush, is it not?
How do you, up here like
a bird in a cage, know all of that?!
I hear a few things, and can figure it out.
I talk to the maids, too.
What are you, a monster?
Understood. Let us drop all pretense.
Prince, you do not mind, do you?
However, before we do, I would like
to speak to the real Princess Renner.
Ah, it's better than I thought!
Those eyes are the eyes
I saw in you as a young child!
Have you been putting on an act?
I had been fulfilled.
Are you referring to Climb?
Yes indeed. If I could be wed to Climb...
hmm, and while I'm at it,
if I could chain him up, and keep him,
so he could not go anywhere,
that might make me even happier.
"Keep" him? In other words,
you are not in love with him?
I am in love with him!
I very much like his eyes!
I also love the way
he follows me around, like a dog.
Sorry, but I'm not following at all.
I am not asking you to understand.
As long as you know that I am fond of him,
and that I love him, that is enough.
However, marrying a commoner such as...
M-Master Climb might be...
Can't we strike a deal? Once I accede
to the throne, I'll hitch you and Climb.
--Count me in!
--That was fast!
From the moment you arrived, Brother,
I wanted to bring that subject up.
I also have a request for you, Marquis Raeven.
What might that be?
Marquis Raeven, you have a son, yes?
Yes, he is still only five.
I ask that he be my betrothed.
No!
You think I would give my boy
to a woman like you?!
P-Pardon me, Your Highnesses.
Would you mind telling me your reasons?
I am sure you already know.
Your Highness would marry my son,
but have children with Climb.
My son would bear children
with whichever woman he loved,
which you could then claim
as your successors. Does that sum it up?
Are you really proposing this
right in front of me?
Ah, you would not want
to learn of it later, would you?
So, I hear you are
going up against Eight Fingers?
Yes. I would like to strike at them
before they burrow underground,
but I am short of soldiers.
Where will you be attacking?
These seven locations.
The problem is that each of these locations
is in a territory owned by a different nobleman.
If we could just uncover something
that ties them with Eight Fingers,
I could use it to exert pressure on the nobles.
Barring that, we can just find something, right?
It's definite where they dispose
of their incriminating materials.
Also, my sister, I have an important question.
Our beloved older brother, the first prince,
is also taking money from Eight Fingers, right?
Ah, Brother Barbro?
This would be the
perfect evidence to depose him.
I'd like to include the drug division
stronghold he deals with in your plans.
Then that will make eight places for us to raid.
As far as manpower, I will send my own
guardsmen and the factions' soldiers.
However, while we may have enough numbers,
whether we can go up against Six Arms,
which is said to be
adamantite class, is the question.
I have a request in
at the adventurer's guild, too.
He's here.
This is a gentleman who may help us.
That took a bit of time, but we did
finish arrangements to transport the grain,
so now we can return
to Nazarick without any issues.
Tuare! Tuare, are you here?!
There are a number of fresh marks
around the front door's keyhole.
I believe there is a good chance
that someone picked the lock.
Tuare has been kidnapped,
which means that I am going to rescue her.
A time and place have been
carefully spelled out here.
I wonder if that is the best course.
I just mean that before you go,
we should inform Lord Ains.
Lord Sebas, have you
forgotten his words earlier?
Report this to Lord Ains.
Tell him that Tuare has been kidnapped,
and ask what we should do about it.
Albedo...
Y-Yes, Lord Ains? Is something the matter?
I just got a message from Sebas--
or rather, Solution--
and apparently, the woman that
Sebas took in, Tuare, has been abducted.
I am otherwise occupied at the moment.
I need you to put together
some forces to back Sebas up.
Lord Ains, please permit me
the folly of raising an objection,
but is there any value in saving
an inferior creature such as a human?
Albedo, I promised to save Tuareninya
in the name of Ains Ooal Gown. Is that clear?
Is that clear?! I promised her
my protection, in my name, no less!
Even if they did not know,
this cannot be allowed to stand!
Sorry.
There is nothing for which
you need to apologize, Lord Ains!
Your order is received.
In addition to rescuing her,
I will see that the hammer falls on
those lowly humans who have upset you!
Tell you what. You organize them,
and Demiurge will command them onsite.
Still, I don't understand.
Ains Ooal Gown...
This is ridiculous.